**Don Joseph**172 Starwood Drive Guelph, ON • (226) 500-1428 • d9joseph@uwaterloo.ca
• https://github.com/mtvdonpablo

	SUMMARY	YOF (	<b>DUALIFI</b>	CATIONS
--	---------	-------	----------------	---------

☐ Proficient with data structures and algorithms using Python in Intro to Computer Science II.			
☐ Self-taught <b>HTML</b> and <b>CSS</b> to build a portfolio website.			
☐ Knowledge of the <b>Software Development Cycle</b> and experience w	with User Acceptance Testing		
☐ Proficient in <b>debugging</b> and <b>maintaining</b> software systems			
□ Proven organizational <b>analysis</b> and <b>problem-solving</b> skills			
EDUCATION			
University of Waterloo, Waterloo, ON.			
Candidate for Bachelor of Mathematics with experiential education certific	cate 2019-Present		
Major in Information Technology Management			
PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES			
Jr. Systems Developer	May 2023–August 2023		
Co-operators Group Limited, Regina, Saskatchewan			
☐ Collaborated with business partners to gather requirements.			
☐ Automated IBM Ingenium processes.			
☐ Utilized C#, SQL, and libraries to design and build 3 robust and de	pendable automations.		
☐ Worked in an agile framework leveraging DevOps and Bitbucket.			
<b>Robotic Process Automation Developer Intern</b>	May 2022–December 2022		
Co-operators Group Limited, Guelph, Ontario			
<ul> <li>Managed the full Software Development Lifecycle: Design, Build, Production support.</li> </ul>	Unit Test, Peer Review and		
☐ Developed a finance business process that returns 1040 staff hours	per year to the business.		
☐ Enhanced 15+ automation in support of production defects and req	= -		
Contributed to saving 2294 staff hours and helped achieve the goal 2022.			
Bookkeeper	March 2020-January 2021		
Fusion Indian Cuisine, Guelph, Ontario	•		
☐ Catalogued 5-8 invoices using QuickBooks weekly in preparation to	for taxes and budgeting.		
☐ Verified 15-20 transactions weekly to check for errors or fraud.			
☐ Oversaw accounts payable using QuickBooks to help produce an a	ccurate balance sheet.		
☐ Managed the payment of suppliers, ensuring timely and accurate pa	ayments.		
Server L	December 2018-January 2020		
Fusion Indian Cuisine, Guelph, Ontario	•		
☐ Greeted guests and provided excellent customer service to ensure g	guests enjoyed their meal.		
Served food, cleaned tables, and multitasked in a fast-paced environment.			
Handled cash and closed cash register, ensured an accurate cash float.			
☐ Dealt with frustrated customers and made ethical decisions that ber			
CERTIFICATION			